Hi, my name is Peter Carter.
You don't remember me, but I have
something to tell you that's going to
sound crazy.
But it's the truth.
And I know you're going to believe me
because you're very good at telling what
I'm lying.
Evie, can you check the calibration of
my targeting matrix? That doesn't feel
zeroed in to me. Checking target
calibration.
Hey, take five.
Standing by.
We used to know each other.
We were together.
But something bad was going to happen,
and the only way to stop it was to make
everyone forget me.
First bit!
MJ, come on. Including you.
Pretend like you're not the happiest
you've ever been in your entire life
right now.
I can't.
Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man.
And sometimes, Spider-Man has to do the
hard things, and if it breaks, Peter
Parker's hard.
And maybe that's my responsibility.
to live alone with the truth.
But the truth is, MJ, that I love you.
And I hope that deep down, something
inside of you remembers that you love
me, too.
Suspect is 5'8", 5'10". See you, Mel.
But until then, I'm just going to be
spying.
This is what happened. We painted Bob
Spider-Man yesterday.
Is anybody ever at the locker room?
I don't know if they like the spectrum.
We've just been using it for so long.
Perfect.
Hey everyone, sophomore year and then
it's back.
Older, wiser, flyer.
Let's go.
Whoa. What? It's on your face.
How do you know about it? I mean, you
look like an assistant coach.
Is he here, Spidey?
If I drop him for you, how long will you
take to hit the ground?
I don't know.
You tell me.
Let's get this on a high note, huh?
You trying to take my job, Simon?
Hey, you guys are the professionals. I'm
just a volunteer.
It's a new New York.
Thanks to Spider-Man's crime rates, it's
dropped to a record low.
Police and damage control give much of
the credit to the Mac Heroes. Appreciate
it, Hudson.
Armed robbery at City Union Bank.
In the past six months, he has taken
down every major crime ward across the
five boroughs, including the superpower
ninja group that has.
He is the pride of New York City.
You know, every grown-up relies on him,
and every kid wants to be.
Final semester at MIT.
Oh, my God, for graduating in a month.
He's made so many memories. Where do I
begin?
Nice swimming in the Charles River with
Jim and Wiley.
The infamous food fight at the Banana
Lounge.
Pulling all-nighters and studs by with
MJ and Nate Dow.
It feels like yesterday I was sitting on
a roof with MJ dreaming about coming
here together. I still can't believe we
did it.
I'm so grateful for all the friends that
I've made. I couldn't imagine going to
this with anyone else.
Dad, who do you think is actually
watching this? Uh, I don't know. Maybe
someone? What?
No!
Yeah,
I hear you, but can you prove it? Yeah,
we're going through his financial
records and we're following his crew
every night.
Do you do anything besides work?
You know what I'm saying? You do
something you love. You don't work a day
in your life.
Mom, where's my calculator?
Trust me, all right?
Being married to the job never ends
well.
Oh, don't worry about it. I'll be okay.
Oh, yeah?
You still getting them headaches,
though?
Uh, yeah, but, um...
But I'll be fine. I don't know, man. I
think your body's trying to tell you
something. Like you need to get out of
that suit every once in a while.
Mom, do you know where my calculator is?
I don't know, Poppy.
What you need is the real human
connection.
Oh, what? We're not connecting?
Nah, dude.
I don't know your name, your face, or
nothing about you.
I don't think you've ever asked me a
question about my life. Sure I have.
Yeah, what am I connecting?
Uh, well, for starters, your son's
name's Poppy.
And his Spider-Man?
I can't tell you this, sweetheart.
Not me, Mr. Spider-Man.
Oh, God.
A hijacked tank is heading southbound
past 34th Street. All available units
respond. Hey, you getting this?
More work. Lucky you.
Okay, I'll see you out there. I'm so
sorry, I gotta go.
No, no, I don't need to...
I didn't know it just by looking at it,
but this very street was completely
destroyed in the Battle of New Orleans.
Yo.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
Are you going to stop that thing or
what?
Heading straight for the damage control
detention center.
I'm trying.
Try harder. There's a lot of scary loot
blocks up in there. Who do you think put
them in there?
Let's go, Scorpion.
Get out of the vehicle, ma'am.
I was thinking the same thing.
Keep everything.
There is a building.
Enjoy the rest, Scorpion.
Scorpion team, let's lay down in the
cheaper bag.
Scorpions are eternal, man.
You can see me.
Tell me who you are.
You first.
You pushed
me out.
Interesting. What the hell was that?
Did you just try to jump into my mind?
No. The whole time they've been chasing
me.
You guys are asking yourself a very
important question.
What's that thing?
Spider-Man?
What just happened?
You guys okay? You good?
I swear, all the things they said I did,
I don't remember doing any of them. It's
okay, it's okay. Look, let these people
take a carry. I would never hurt you.
Okay. I love you, sweetheart. Yeah, all
right, buddy, all right.
Hey, what do you got? Here, get this.
Chopper took Scorpion to Bellevue. Ten
minutes later, a guard walked in right
out the door. What?
Mm-hmm.
What about the tank?
Stolen from a damage control warehouse
in Brooklyn.
Driver was a janitor before there.
You got a motive?
Not on.
And no criminal record?
Scorpion must have gotten to us somehow.
Yeah, maybe.
What do you mean, maybe?
I mean, I don't know.
But I know someone that might.
Where are you going?
You keep following the lead, Don
Scorpion. I'm going to go talk to
someone.
Is this 3250 Brighton Beach?
Okay.
I think I know what that means.
Take off your clothes.
Uh, what?
You don't wear clothes in Tasmania.
They're just a leotard.
This is not a leotard.
Your text said that this was your
office.
This is my office.
Get in.
Fine, thanks. I'll just... My office, my
room.
This way, you get to enjoy a nice,
relaxing talk, and I get to see that you
don't have any weapons, and we both win.
I've seen it.
It's hard to unsee to be honest. But
look, I don't have anyone. I just kind
of keep to myself.
Oh, but you're sad all the time?
I wonder if you feel sad.
Can we just talk about when I came here
to talk to you about the attack on
damage control?
Yes. So that is more your area.
Like small potato stuff.
Whereas the new Avengers are focusing on
big potato stuff.
Right. Okay. Well, there's more to it
than that. You know, the driver and the
others who were helping. Like someone
was looking at you.
And you're wondering if it's mind
control.
Exactly. Like how they used on me in the
red room. Exactly. And the other
weirdos. Right. Right. No, I don't think
so. I actually think it's probably more
like possession.
Possession?
As a ghost, or a demon, or in Russia we
have leshy, leshy.
Wolves can fart and can possess.
Sorry.
Whatever it is, they're looking for
something.
This is the fourth attack on the damage
control facility in the room.
What do you think they're looking for?
I don't know.
But you know what?
After the attack today, there was a
cross-agency cybersecurity alert that
got triggered.
Someone accessed the damage control
restricted server using credentials from
13 police on the way station.
They all searched for the same thing.
What does that mean?
It could be alien tech, or secretive
weapon programs, or
launch codes, or... I don't know. This
is for you to figure out. This is
plumbed baby potato stuff, not baby
potato brain stuff.
Jeez, maybe I'll just go ask damage
control myself.
You know, you're not completely
anonymous anymore.
I figured.
Belly button.
Okay, bye.
appointment with, uh... Director
Metzger. Yes. Please step through the
scanner.
Enhanced human detected.
Superior strength.
Superior agility.
Heightened senses.
Exogenous DNA.
Arachnid.
Please remove your face covering for
identity scan.
Oh, no, I can't do that. Failure to
remove your face covering will result in
defensive measures.
Defensive measures? What are you talking
about?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, guys, guys, guys, I
can't take my mask off.
Spider-Man.
He's all right.
My apologies.
We are so glad you're here.
Bill Metzger, Director of Damage
Control.
How are you?
I'm good, thank you.
We have to beef up security around here,
but I hope we didn't give you a fright.
No, not at all. All right, come on this
way.
This floor is mostly research and
administrative.
Down there, we have incident cleanup,
laboratory, agent training.
Hey, what are they doing? It's okay.
The hand works for us now.
After you brought them in, I realized
that fundamentally they're a group of
kids without a leader.
All they needed was a little direction.
And suddenly all the things that made
them dangerous turned them into an
invaluable part of our security team.
You can look at the many fronts that
face us and see only danger.
But you can see opportunity.
Wow, look at that.
In the hands of Docker, these are
nuisance.
That doesn't mean we can't buy from the
technology or respect the innovation.
Our mission is to redirect destructive
energy to something useful.
That's the true meaning of damage
control.
Be careful with that!
President Lloyd?
I, uh, wanted to talk to you about the
recent attacks on the agency.
There's been four, right?
Please, have a seat.
You are right.
It appears we're faced with a threat we
can't control.
One we can't even see.
But you can.
I saw the security footage.
I also read Detective DeWolf's report.
I believe you understand exactly what
we're up against.
Someone or something that can hop into
people's minds.
But not yours?
No. I mean, it tried, but it couldn't.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
We're on our heels right now.
God forbid if we were to get in here and
find whatever it is it's looking for,
the consequences could be...
unimaginable.
Let me get whatever it's looking for in
that giant vault.
There are some things, because of the
nature of my job, I cannot tell you.
But I believe you're our best defense
against this.
You're the only one who can sense it.
You're the only one who's immune to it.
I'm counting on you to defeat it.
That's a pretty good speech, Director.
I'll do everything that I can, I
promise.
Well, then consider yourself a friend of
Damage Control.
Thanks.
I'll be in touch.
Oh, I wanted to ask.
The phrase VMAX doesn't mean anything to
you, does it?
No.
Where'd you hear that?
Oh, I just, you know, thank you for
being a superhero. There are some things
I just can't tell you.
Anyway, I'll see you later.
You guys are doing great. Keep it up.
I don't think Metzger knows any more
than we do, but I told him I'd do
whatever I can to help.
You want to help?
The best thing you could do is find
Scorpion. He's our only lead. Yeah, I
know. I have every camera in the city
running official recognition scan for
him. That sounds super illegal,
Spider-Man. I'm going to pretend I
didn't hear that.
Yeah, probably for the best.
But look, if he shows his face, we'll
know. Do you have any, any tips?
No, not yet.
I'll call you back.
Uh-huh.
It's easy.
Hey,
uh,
also, you got any sharp fire energy?
Yeah.
Oh, no, no, no. I don't want any. That
stuff will kill you.
All my friends were drinking them during
finals, and now they're addicted.
So I'm going to need you to not sell me
any.
Memorize my face?
Please, do not sell this guy any short
fire.
Sure. Whatever.
Actually, I'll take one.
The last one.
Maybe two.
And then never sell me any.
I'll get it right.
See, you've stumbled across my board.
I'm not one of those weirdos, I swear.
He actually saved me and my friends'
lives a few times in high school.
Oh, cool.
Yeah, yeah.
Ever since, I've just been trying to
figure out who he is.
Not to unmask him to the world or
anything, just to, you know, hopefully
thank him face-to-face.
I actually created this app that
monitors your sightings.
Well, you created his body tracker.
You heard of it. Nice.
Where is Spider-Man?
Little chat room right there.
Now, we know he's definitely from
Queens.
Not the biggest revelation.
But I have been able to narrow it down
to two prime suspects.
Yeah. If you knew who they were, it
would really blow your mind. I'm sure.
Ned, by the way.
Oh, I'm, um... Well, there's like 50
people in our apartment.
Statistically speaking, it means like
two of them are sociopaths. Which is
kind of cool.
Nice flowers.
Oh, they're, uh, housewarming gifts.
Really? Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Most people just brought beer and chips.
That's very nice.
Uh, I'm MJ.
I'm, uh, I'm, uh, Maynard.
Maynard.
You two don't know each other?
No, I'm a neighbor.
Friendly neighbor?
Sorry.
So, how was the interview?
I'm gonna go put these in water.
It was nice to meet you, Maeve Nard.
Nerd.
Maeve Nard. Yeah.
Did you go?
Please tell me that you went.
Yeah, so I went.
And?
And I got the job.
Oh my god, that's amazing!
I turned it down.
I don't want to work for some sort of
corporation.
It's not almost soulless.
Okay, they're all mostly soulless, but
don't you want, like, health insurance?
Yeah, of course I do, but at what cost?
Depends on your deductible.
Oh, you mean, like, your principles?
Yeah. Sorry.
I don't know. I know it sounds cheesy,
but something is just telling me that
I'm supposed to be waiting for something
great, you know?
Okay, um, to, uh, wait for something
great.
Waiting for something great.
Well, the wait is over.
Oh!
You're home.
Dude, this is Bob's house.
Just like you.
Oh! I want to hide this.
I lifted this off him again.
What if Ned needs the fire of a thousand
charms?
You need heart palpitations.
You can't save everyone. I can try.
together.
Yeah, sure. Yeah, I'd love that.
Be a fresh soul.
Allow me to get?
Yeah, you're right. You're going to
forget who
I am.
What are you talking about?
It's okay.
I'm going to come and find you.
I'll explain everything.
I don't want to wait.
Why don't you tell me what you did?
My name is Peter Parker, and I would
like a coffee.
Is there anything else?
You think you don't have to listen to me
now that I've got powers?
You know, this whole thing can get
really
scary.
You know that?
Well, yeah, it's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change very quickly.
Ways that we can't even imagine right
now.
Believe me, I know.
What do you mean?
Oh, no!
I uh... I live here, I just um... I'm
gonna grab my stuff.
Oh, keep the mouth.
You have 107 new alerts. Please check
backlog.
What is happening?
The results of your body scan show a
surge in the hormones associated with
your arachnid DNA, resulting in the
formation of organic web spinnerets and
dangerously heightened sensory
receptors.
Okay, but I feel fine.
Prolonged isolation or emotional trauma
could be contributing to this sudden
change. Have you experienced any recent
traumatic events?
Peter?
I'm fine, Edie. You don't seem fine. I
recommend you take some time to
rebalance. Well, that's not really an
option, is it?
Mechanical web shooters and organic webs
cannot be used simultaneously.
are taking in too much information at
once.
Okay.
It's okay.
All right, organic webs.
Peter 2 happened. He was cool.
He was cool.
Oh, my God, that's hideous.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, that didn't work.
Organic webs.
Come on, man!
What's going on, Evie?
Shots fired at the Damage Control Data
Center in Manhattan.
Suspect facial match with Scorpion.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Come on, three.
Scorpion, do we really gotta keep doing
this? My head is killing me.
You think I'm Scorpion?
What's happening, Katie?
Huh.
You can't save me anymore.
You.
What's going on with you, Spider-Man?
Is she okay?
No. It wasn't Scorpion, okay? I mean, it
was... He was possessed by whatever
hijacked that train, okay?
Please, can I just... Slow down.
Listen, I don't know what this is, but I
need you to pull it together.
You almost killed a cop.
This isn't you.
I know, I'm sorry.
If you act like this again, I cannot
protect you.
Whatever this is, you need to fix it.
Through lattice chromodynamics,
We can arrange time and space in a grid,
which allows us to simulate the
quarks binding into the protons.
Cindy, is this the question about
protons or more stuff about Avengers?
Okay. Guys, I love to tell stories, but
you know, I got to teach you some
physics at some point here.
All right. Let it rip, Cindy.
If Thanos is so worried about
overpopulation, Why didn't you use the
magic glove to make more food?
Arthur, you want to answer that
question?
Hulk!
Excuse me, Dr.
Maddox. Are you okay?
Yeah, sorry. It's just a headache.
Have you got a minute? I wanted to talk
to you about your inhibitor.
Oh, sure.
Don't worry. We've got fail-safe. I'm
not going to turn into the big green
raging monster machine in the cafeteria.
But if you do see me with this thing
off, run.
No,
but you're using target-specific
short-interfering RNA, right?
It's like gene silencing, you're just
incorporating the gamma radiation.
What'd you say your name was?
Uh, Ned.
So you found a way to suppress the
expression of DNA even as it's
undergoing the mutation due to gamma
radiation, right? Yes.
Okay, so my question is, would that same
thing be possible with DNA that's
mutating for another reason?
What's the reason?
I don't know.
Let's say that the host genome is mixed
with some kind of foreign DNA.
Theoretically.
Theoretically, yes, that's possible.
Yes.
to press on these young parts of that
DNA expression.
Like the bad aspects, but just keep all
the good stuff.
You mean, like if I wanted to keep some
parts of hope and not others?
Right. It would be enormously dangerous
and complex, but if you were able
to target the correct mRNA strand?
Possibly. Wait, so you could just turn
the mutating gene on and off as long as
you do it before the mRNA transcription?
Maybe.
I mean, if you apply the same thinking,
you could even develop some kind of
automatic inhibitor that would just
adjust to any type of mutation.
Well, now you're talking about a
universal inhibitor that would control
anyone who has any powers.
It's a dangerous idea.
Well, yeah, but it's theoretical, right?
You're not one of my students, are you?
I'm a grad student.
I've taken enough of your time. I've got
to get some books back to the library.
The library is that way.
Right. Right.
How would you decide?
What's that?
Old parts of nature are good or bad.
What if you're trying to control the
expression of something that needs to be
expressed?
Good luck with your studies, Ed.
Thank you, Professor.
Fourth inhibitor
prototype complete.
Upload inhibitor.
Uploaded.
Would you like to run a test?
Yeah, run it.
Several days.
Spiders have three stages in their life
cycle.
Each stage is characterized by physical
changes, with the largest changes
occurring during the beautiful
transition to adulthood.
For those who make it through, molting
amounts to a kind of fever.
Can you turn that spider stuff off? Turn
it off video.
Inhibitor. Keep an eye on my vitals.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing arachnid hormones to your
baseline level.
Okay.
All right, Amy.
Let's do this.
Initiating field test one.
That's working.
Alert. Inhibitor is overheating.
Functionality reducing.
Yeah. I'm sensing that.
Alert. Sensing overload.
Alert.
Web grenades activated.
There we go.
Yo, Spider-Man!
You okay?
Yeah, I'm just trying out some new tech.
Oh, yeah?
To get rid of that monster inside you?
You okay, Anthony, huh?
Guess your technology isn't working.
You know, you're the only person I've
met that I can't... Hop into.
I'm sure that's really frustrating for
you.
Well, I'll get in there one day. What do
you want?
I don't know why a half-human,
half-spider would decide to work for an
organization whose sole mission is to
hunt down anybody who's different.
Damage Control isn't after you because
you're different.
They're hunting you down because you're
dangerous. Now, what do you want?
Since you're a very simple spider, let
me spell it out for you.
Damage control is something that I need.
Oh, you mean VMAX?
I was planning to use Scorpion to get
it, but you keep getting in my way.
I will always be in your way. Oh, are
you sure about that, Peter Parker?
You know, your apartment is kind of like
a parody where you think a sad single
guy with money is my bitch.
Bain powder container.
Freeway.
Protein powder?
You're bluffing.
You know, you're not hard to track down,
Peter.
Well, at least not for someone like me.
I did find one interesting thing,
though.
In the wrong places.
Coffee cup.
Easy display home workstation.
You spent four years erasing Peter
Parker from existence?
No wonder this body's trying to swallow
up the man.
I wonder if MJ would even recognize him.
I think I might go see how she's doing.
I'm not going to let that happen. No,
her roommate was nice enough to post a
new address online.
How about if I erase it?
You touch her, and it starts winning.
I'm fast.
You better make up your mind.
He's being tracked for physical
anomalies.
Searching for physical anomalies between
subjects.
Please stand by.
Thank you all so much for coming today.
I'm sorry about that.
Give it up for Spider-Man.
It raised for the love of his life, and
it's not looking good.
Come on, Spidey.
Hip-hop.
Sorry.
Excuse me. Run these numbers with the
others.
Calculating. Calculation complete.
I don't see anybody up here for you to
hop into.
Like I said, you're not getting me.
Time for this. Please, come on. You need
to get out of my apartment.
But this is going to sound insane, but
there is someone who is after you who is
really dangerous, okay? And I promised
you that I would keep you safe.
Please, you just have to trust me. Come
on.
Are you okay? Yeah, I'm fine. Okay.
We should be safe up here.
Okay, well, safe from what?
I'm not entirely sure.
Okay, well, what do they want with me?
I don't know.
You don't know?
It doesn't make any sense. Why would
they choose me?
I wish I could tell you. I just... We
knew each other, didn't we?
What?
That's the only explanation.
It's been driving me crazy for years,
all the times that Spider-Man saved
either me or Ned.
It was the Washington Monument, and then
it was London, and Prague, and the Night
Monkey.
I mean, twice as a coincidence, but over
and over again.
We knew each other. Tell me I'm wrong.
Wait, you're wrong.
What were we? Were we classmates or
friends or something?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Were we something more?
I just, I can't.
I can't remember and I feel like someone
scrambled my brain and you're the only
one who would know why.
This is crazy. I know that you can't
tell me the truth.
But I need to know.
Maybe there's a part of me that still
remembers.
Go ahead,
Peter.
Touch her.
Hold her.
You've been wanting to do this so long.
True love's kiss breaks the spell and
reunites the star-crossed lovers.
I'm Jamie Fonda.
You really are a simple spider, aren't
you?
I see why you like her.
She's, uh... She's smart.
Funny.
A little dark and twisted.
I mean, it is sad.
There is, like, no thoughts of you in
here.
Once or never.
But you knew that, didn't you?
You're a mother.
If you loved someone the way that I love
her, then you'd know that what you're
doing right now is unforgivable.
All of that, though.
You know, some people...
You're running out of time, Peter.
It's good enough that it won't just be
your friends who don't remember Peter
Parker.
Maybe you should write a letter to
yourself.
There's a monster up here.
You win, you win, you win. Just don't
hurt her.
You're a mess, Spider-Man.
Anytime I want.
I can be anyone I want.
So you can't protect MJ.
Even from herself.
It really is a nice letter.
A little heavy-handed.
Not bad.
I'm going to take you someplace safe.
Take me to 3165.
Navigating to Empire State University.
Can we just slow down for like two
seconds, please? We're almost there.
Yeah, yeah, but you just told me I was
mind-controlled.
Well, not technically. If you're lucky,
I believe in that stuff, okay? Because
governments have been doing it for
years, especially the French.
Are you okay?
Yeah, gee, look, sorry. I'm just trying
to make you someplace safe, okay?
Oh, I'm so safe.
You're losing it, kid.
Thought you'd be able to see that coming
a mile away.
What is wrong with you? You could have
killed us. Excuse me? You show up to my
house and ask what you think is going to
happen. Wait, this is your house? What
the hell is that?
What the hell are you?
She's, um, uh, you know.
No, I don't know. That's why I just
asked.
She's in danger, Frank. Look, I need
your help, okay?
Yeah, looks like it. Well, come on. You
owe me.
Ah, come on. That's your sick-headed
story. Staten Island.
That's Staten Island. What more do you
want me to do? I literally saved your
life. Get out of your mind, kid. I gotta
save it twice to get back to you? That
guy's gonna hit me with a handful of
rice. What does that sound like to you?
I have exactly what I want. I see you
right there. I know exactly what I want.
Take that junkie a little back. Okay,
fine. Go ahead. What does that sound
like to you?
Okay, I just want to go home.
That's an excellent idea.
Kick rocks. No, no, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Please.
I have got to keep her safe, okay? And I
don't have anywhere else to go.
You like chili?
I made chili.
All right. Watch out for the claymores.
I won't pick up pieces of you for the
next two weeks.
I definitely would not eat that chili.
So you're telling me that maniac behind
all that tank nonsense is nothing but a
goddamn teenager.
And it's not just a tank. It's every
attack on damage control this past
month. I think you did learn how to
drive a tank.
I don't know, Frank.
Beat your ass all over the street like
that. She did not beat my ass.
This is him?
You should get the hell away from that.
Look, I got one rule in this house.
You don't touch anything.
Don't move anything.
You sure as shit don't ask me any
goddamn questions about anything.
So three rules.
Ask you why you like her.
Go put some pants on.
Don't touch the chili.
I like him.
Of course you do.
So I managed to pull the zimmies from my
HUD and I'm ready to do this.
Who is she? A couple months ago, nobody.
She was in and out of foster care, psych
hospitals, and then eventually she ran
away and dropped off the grid.
There's hardly any information about her
that hasn't been scrubbed, but she
classified as a telepath, and now we
have a name.
Jean Gray.
Yeah.
These are the damage control sites that
she hasn't hit yet.
So, if she services, then my facial
tracking program will pick her up.
Right. Oh, yeah? What then?
Well, don't worry about what then. Just
look after her.
Don't worry about it, huh?
You're supposed to sit here and babysit
your girlfriend?
I don't want to. She's my girlfriend.
All right, look, what's the plan, huh?
Just kind of hope that your facial
tracking program works?
You get yourself killed, I got to watch
her the rest of my life. I'm not going
to get killed, Frank. I can catch her,
okay? I just have to fix my inhibitor
and then I'll be good to go.
What do you need to do that?
Frank, you do not have what I need to do
that, okay?
Hey, you got some mouth on you. What do
you think you have, an anti-static mat,
a total probe with micro tools?
I got all that shit.
What for?
Bingo.
I'm leaving home.
Hey, do you think it's safe to maybe
call someone and let them know I'm okay?
Uh... Like your boyfriend?
No, like my roommate.
Oh, um...
I don't think that's such a good idea,
you know, because she already knows who
he is and she can inhabit anyone she
wants. Right, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're right.
Sorry. No, it's fine. I totally get it.
If I called my boyfriend, he'd just ask
me a bunch of questions that I couldn't
answer and then he'd tell me I was being
withholding again.
Withholding? Yep.
Sounds like your boyfriend's kind of a
jerk.
Why do you think you're withholding?
I don't know. You tell me, masked
vigilante behind the curtain.
Um, okay,
I see your point.
So what about you?
What about me?
Well, do you have Mrs.
Spider-Man?
Do I have Mrs. Spider-Man?
Um... No.
No.
Why not?
Why not? Because I'm... I'm too
withholding, obviously.
Welcome to the club.
There was someone.
Huh? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What happened?
I, uh... I had to let her go.
To keep her safe.
Sorry, that must have been really hard
for you.
Yeah, it was, yeah.
It is.
It is really hard.
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm okay. What? It's
kind of cold. Hold on, hold on, hold on,
hold on, hold on.
What's going on?
It just keeps overheating on me.
It's been stomping me for days.
Before I switched to aerospace, I was
going to major in biochemical
engineering.
Do you mind if I... Oh, yeah, for sure.
Here.
There you go.
So, does the device itself, I mean, does
it generate any kind of radiation or a
magnetic field? Because that would
definitely interfere.
Well, yeah, it has a micro magnetic
field, but I accounted for that in the
design. Okay, well, what about your
suit?
Oh, it actually dissipates into the
fabric, which is pretty cool.
Okay.
What about those?
What about what?
Your goggles.
Or whatever you call them. Uh, they
would create a field. It would be tiny,
but... But it's on your head, which is
very close to the inhibitor. Which is
probably why it's overheating. Oh, and
that is genius.
Okay, this has to work.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing selected arachnid hormones.
Okay, that feels better.
That feels totally better.
Oh, my head feels so clear.
And I'm not shooting organic webs. Oh,
my God, Angie, that, like, totally
worked.
You know, this isn't really intense
stuff you're working on here.
Well, yeah, it's really important.
Yeah, but this is, like, I mean, this
is, like, altering your DNA.
I mean, this is the kind of stuff you
put on, like, I don't know, like a
monster?
Well, if you've seen what's been
happening to me over the last couple
days, then you might understand.
Yeah, well, I've been with you for the
last few hours, and that's not what I've
seen.
Then what have you seen?
From my side of the curtain.
I really could die.
I might just be changing.
I don't need to overstep all that.
I'll get back to it.
You want coffee?
Sure.
Get your shit fixed.
Yeah, I've been wearing it all night.
So far so good.
I made this other one universal.
So if I could get it on Jean, it should
completely shut down her powers.
You know what else would work?
You just shoot her.
Nice.
That's crazy.
That's got to be the goofiest shit I've
ever seen in my life. You can't even
take the mask off. Drink a cup of
coffee.
I'll take it personally, Frank. It stays
on for everybody.
Even her?
Who is she, kid?
I don't know. Ah, that's horse shit. Who
is she? I'm telling you, I don't know
who she is. You care about her. I don't
care about her. Look, I don't know who
she is, Frank, okay? I don't have
anybody. I'm like you. I just keep to
myself. You're like me.
What do you know about me, kid?
You think this is a choice? Living like
this is a lifestyle?
Is that what you think?
Kid, this is a sentence.
If I had one second, people I love are
still breathing. You think I'd be hiding
behind a mask?
You think I'd pretend to be something
that I'm not?
Acting like a goddamn coward?
I got a facial match.
She's at the damage control HQ in
Manhattan.
I gotta go. Okay.
She's gonna be okay.
I'll see to it.
Hey.
You're just gonna let him go by himself?
You know, I think he might need you.
Kind of like you needed him on set now.
You can't hide from me forever, Bill.
You've got a strong door, but it's the
one you have to worry about.
Who are you and what do you want?
I'm Jeannie Gray, and you know what I
want.
I don't want everybody to hear this.
Gene?
You woke me up?
I'm blushing.
I told you what would happen to your
girl if you got in my way.
You're not getting near her again.
You're definitely not getting inside
that vault.
Maybe not.
But this guy might.
Gene, you don't know what you're dealing
with.
You know, you and Banner have a lot in
common.
I'm fighting a losing battle against a
monster that lives inside you.
Gene, this is the Hulk you can't def-
What
the hell?
Oh, I see.
Trying to muzzle me like you muzzle
yourself.
I can't let you in there.
Whatever VMAX is, you're not getting it.
Like hell I'm not.
I told you to stay home and watch him.
Yeah, you did.
And then she tells me I gotta come watch
you.
Wait, did she actually say that to you?
Are you blushing? I have to go.
God
damn
it. I can do it before I pick her up.
That's a good idea. Bring her up and go.
What are you gonna do? Do you want to
live to death? No, look. Change your
plan.
First we get this on the Hulk, then we
go after him.
I got one better.
That's the highest casualty producing
thread. You contain it. I go find the
source. I take it down. You got it?
Are you just trying to get out and fight
in the hole?
What are you doing?
Okay, whatever, dude. I got this.
Hold your breath. Do not kill her.
Don't start with that soft serve
bullshit.
I'm going to do this. I'm going to do it
my way. Just go.
Just go.
Don't get within 33 feet.
So frustrating.
Hey. Oh, no.
No, not again.
Oh, no.
Dr. Banner?
Is that you?
Spider-Man, what happened?
Where am I?
Hey, hey, hey. Did I do all this?
God. Did I hurt anyone?
It's not your fault. She was in your
mind. She wasn't in control.
I've lost my inhibits. Look, here, here.
They're always been keeping the monster
inside. It's okay. I got another one. I
just need you to put this on. What is
this? Universal. It should work on you.
Please, for the people in the building,
put it on.
You okay?
My head.
I think you broke something.
Is he still in there?
No.
Oh, my God.
Bruce?
I can get you out of here, okay? I just
need you to put that inhibitor on. I
can't get through.
Yes, you can, Bruce. Yes, you can.
Get out of the building.
I didn't know you could get that big.
Look at that, Peter.
to that nature.
Throw down your gun, or you'll get the
next one in the head.
Where is she?
It's over, Gene.
Send my gun.
Save my life.
And you saved God knows how many lives
by making sure she didn't find what she
was looking for in him.
Before she passed out, she tried to say
something.
A name, Sarah.
Does that mean something to you?
Before you got the inhibitor on her, she
managed to get in my mind for a moment.
Sarah was the name of someone I worked
closely with that recently passed.
Sorry to hear that.
Somehow the memory of Sarah must have
affected her.
Well, I'd love to talk to her when she
wakes up.
That's all right. Of course.
She'll be transferred to our facility on
Roosevelt Island.
I'm just as eager to give the talking as
you are. But let's not strain her too
much for one day.
Yeah, of course.
Thank you, Spider-Man.
My pleasure.
One day.
It worked.
She's in custody.
Are you safe?
You love this?
Did you want me to find it?
No.
No. Look,
I can explain.
Can you take that off, please?
What?
I think I deserve to have this
conversation with Peter Parker.
I was trying
to protect you.
I know,
I'm sorry.
So you just were going to make that
decision for me?
I know I'm sorry.
I don't really need you to keep saying
that you're sorry. I don't know what you
want me to tell you. I want you to tell
me why you would do this to me.
I lost someone.
And they'd still be here if it wasn't
for me.
I can read you that letter because...
I didn't want anything like that to
happen to you.
That's not really your decision. I know
it's not, but... And
I've been trying to live my life without
you, but I...
or whatever it is that you did.
They weren't.
All these memories that you're saying
that we have together, I don't... I
don't have them.
And I do see why, you know, she would
love you, the girl you wrote that letter
to, but...
Don't think that what you want to do is
to die for her.
After that, I'm so hopeful that I
never... I won't love you.
Because I don't... I don't even know
you.
Do you mind taking me home?
Thank you. Yeah, sure.
Um,
I'm gonna, uh... Uh, yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Do you want to come up?
Just to say hi to Ned, maybe?
Oh, I'd love that.
a.k.a. Dr. Bruce Banner, is in custody,
currently being transferred to a
psychiatric ward. After years as a
peaceful academic, the question the
world asks today is, what finally is
that?
Hey,
I'm here, bye.
Hey, I'm here, bye. Hey,
Hey, I'm here, bye. You're not going to
believe this, but the Spidey Tracker app
says that Spider-Man is in the direct
vicinity.
Oh yeah? No way, that's crazy.
Uh,
Ned? Spider-Man? Spider-Man, Ned?
It's nice to meet you, Ned.
Oh, I'm not like a weirdo or anything.
He's a little weird.
Why are you here?
Oh, I was on the subway platform, right?
And she was on her phone. Yeah, I got a
little distracted and the train was
coming.
And I just swooped her right up.
Oh my God.
Why has that never happened to me?
So what if you're mid-swing and you
decide you need to pee? Do you just land
on top of a building? What?
Do you drop down to the ground level and
run into a coffee shop and you're like,
hey, it's Spider-Man, I need to pee? Or
do you find a rooftop somewhere?
No, I don't find a rooftop somewhere. Is
this really what you want to be asking
him right now? Yeah, dude, come on, you
can ask me anything. You want to know
how my web shooters work? I mean, I
already know how the web shooters work.
Is that right? Well, there's obviously
some sort of shear-thinning fluid that
is cycling within the chamber, right, so
it can keep its liquid form. And then
when you activate it by pressing on the
triggers, it runs through a Teflon
turbine, and then it hardens when it
interacts with the air.
Right? I mean, not exactly, but... Okay,
okay, well then tell me what's in the
blood fluid. I would guess something
like a long-chain polymer.
Nylon? That's pretty close.
Okay, okay, what about Nomex or... Oh,
Kevlar!
Alright then, keep those secrets.
If you are very good interested with the
dragon, I was very involved.
All I did was simply give your uncle a
little nudge out the door.
Solid reference.
Ooh, bond me time.
You ordered bond me?
I ordered five bond me's. We have
Spider-Man in the apartment. He's going
to get sad.
Sorry about him. He's just like very
excited that you're here. Are you
kidding? It's like the most fun I've had
in years.
I really miss you guys.
You guys really do look like best
friends.
What do you mean?
You should tell him.
He can handle it.
When she was inhabiting you on
the rooftop, she kissed me.
And I kissed her back.
Because I thought it was you, but I
didn't know.
And I'm really sorry.
I just thought you should know.
Thanks for telling me.
I mean, it's not like I remember
anything anyway, so.
Really? Yeah. It was weird. It was like
one second I was sitting at my desk, and
the next second I was lying on the
street.
I don't know, like a light switch went
off.
What? He said you don't remember
anything.
No, why?
I'm sure he said he remembers thinking
about someone named Sarah, but what
you're saying is that you don't remember
anything at all.
I mean, yeah, it was instantaneous.
That's what made it so scary.
He lied to me.
I heard you caught Bleshy.
Yeah, her name's Jean Grey. I need some
help determining the size of the
potatoes. Potatoes? I think that's my
widow.
I think Metzger lied to me about a name.
Can you see if there's a connection
between Jean and someone named Thera?
Hmm, these potatoes sound meager.
Oh, wow, that really is your office.
Well, well, well.
Internet, government records, and a lot
of data related to Jean Grey has been
scrubbed by damage control.
Data about what?
Her sister.
Wait, Jean has a sister?
Hmm.
Sarah Gray.
Also a telepath.
Damage control took her into custody for
study and observation.
Wow. I mean, you can probably guess what
they mean by that.
Experimentation in other human rights
violations? Yes, exactly.
Wait, who are you?
Hi, Deadly's. Hi!
I'm sorry. I'm just so happy that the
dead man has friends.
Thanks. I, uh, I owe you one.
Good luck, Spider-Man.
Bye. She was just looking for her
sister, and I handed her to the people
who took her.
I gotta go.
Did you see her?
Be careful, all right?
Yeah, we will.
Spider-Man's gonna be here.
Jean, who do you want to be?
Her. Pink jacket.
She's too far.
You're gonna pop.
Pop?
First, pick someone close.
And then...
A chop is a limit, but you can string
them together and go as far as you want.
And when you let go,
you run back where you started.
Could he do that to everyone in this
park at once?
You know, maybe one day, he'd get really
good.
How could she just send it away?
She wasn't really a mom.
Not like that, anyway. She was.
Fully changed.
Yeah, well, if that's all it takes for
you to stop being a mom, then you're not
a mom.
What would you do if you had daughters
like us?
I'd love them.
Especially the redheads. Shut up.
We are the other.
Do we have ice cream?
Want to mix it up with chocolate? Yeah.
Subject is awake.
Heart rate is 94 BPM.
Gene, that's not going to work anymore.
Thanks for inspiring me.
Gene.
I need you to breathe.
I need you to look at me and breathe.
Okay. You're safe.
Breathe.
Where is she?
Like your sister, you've been blessed
with a power that has the potential to
do tremendous good in the world, or
tremendous damage.
A power like yours in the hands of a
child is an impossible burden.
But imagine if that power was placed in
the hands of people who actually know
what to do with it.
Where is my sister?
You're going to change the world, Jane.
What you doing?
Oh, yeah, how's that?
Got eyes everywhere, kid.
Look, Frank, Samson's gonna kidnap
Dean's sister. Dean was just trying to
find her. He was all about everything.
That metal horse shit.
You've seen what she can do and what
she's capable of. What, you're gonna let
her loose? Is that what you're gonna do?
I can tell you right now, you knew that.
Now you're gonna look my way.
Distance checked.
Forty-fifths down. Flogging down the
room.
Flogging down.
Distance is inevitable.
Change of powers are now fully
operational.
As you can tell, you're beyond your jump
rings.
Tell me what VMAX is.
You're the second person to ask me about
that. I have no idea what that means.
She sent me a message.
She was trying to help me find her.
She communicated with you telepathically
across all that distance?
We did register a huge spike in that
session.
Fascinating. What does it mean, asshole?
I don't know.
Let's begin.
I
work
with Sarah Stungeon on two areas.
Identifying the source of her power and
identifying a path towards copying it.
If we could find a way to record a
telepathic brain during a jump.
But perhaps we could replicate those
pathways in the mind of our choosing.
This instrument is your sister's legacy.
We built this together over many months
of trial and error.
I hope you and I can honor her
sacrifice.
What are you talking about?
Sort of the first jump.
Tell me.
What VMAX is.
I know that's where you're hiding her.
She's jumping.
Copy.
We're in full lockdown.
Process has commenced.
What process?
Hey, whoa, that's a pretty serious look
there, dude.
Hey, whoa, what the hell, man? Come on,
I'm a friend of Damage Control. What are
you doing?
Huh, it's going to be like that if you
want to go.
All right, all right, just give me a
sec.
Give me a sec.
I'm not in high school anymore.
Did you stretch? Are you a big
stretcher? I mean, you should do it in
your line of work.
What about you? Are you a bad stretcher?
It's so good for you.
You ready?
What the heck?
Recording's not dead.
Excuse me, sir.
We have injury.
You were right.
He's much stronger than his history.
Increase the frequency.
You're doing very well, Jane.
The last thing my sister saw was this
room. One of the rain waves is somehow
affecting the objects around her. Shut
it down. I'm trying, sir. What do you
mean you're trying?
The last thing my sister saw was this
goddamn room!
Shut it down!
I can't, sir.
I can't let you do that, Bill.
The only hands that will wield this
power are mine.
What do you want?
Jean, I'm here to help you.
You put me here.
I know, and I'm sorry about Sarah, and
I'm sorry that I got it so wrong.
If you came here to save a helpless girl
from damage control, you're too late.
They're the ones who need saving.
And now, so do you.
Here we go.
Please,
please, please.
your friends from damage control and
developed a special weapon just for you.
They've got a whole task force ready.
Just in case you ever get out of line.
People are monsters.
You shouldn't trust them any more than
you trust you.
You got to bum, kid.
You got to hold everyone within a
kilometer of the island.
Wait, what?
My sister died in this room.
Surrounded by these men.
And her only crime was that she was
special.
Just like you.
Just like me.
People like us don't live a normal life.
We don't need to have friends.
Or a family.
Those people are gone.
That life is over.
So why don't you just be honest with
yourself?
Are you Peter Parker?
Or are you Spider-Man?
This won't make it right.
Come on, you're not a killer, Jean.
She has no idea what I am.
I know that you loved your sister.
And I know that losing her felt like you
lost everything.
If you come any closer, he dies.
They all do.
Don't be so sure it can't get into your
mind.
I'm a lot more powerful than they'll
ever try.
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen to me
now that I've got palace?
You know, this
whole thing can get really scary.
You know that?
It's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change very quickly.
Ways that we can't even imagine right
now.
I know.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
I hope that that will always make you
feel really great about yourself.
But I know, sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes it'll be really lonely.
And sometimes, because you're special,
people can be dark, monstrous things to
you.
But,
is what I want you to know.
You're beautiful and the people who love
you, they love you not because you're
special, they love you because you're
you.
I want you to remember that.
You know when it feels like you're
totally alone?
That's your deepest responsibility.
Never forget that no matter No matter
how powerful you
I'm sorry about your aunt.
Yeah, you would have loved her.
Just because we've lost someone, it
doesn't mean we have to do
this alone.
I mean, we can, but trust me, I've been
trying.
Nothing's ever...
Even if that's true.
I have no one.
You hurt?
Fine.
I'm okay.
Peter. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Peter.
Peter. Peter.
No, no, no, no.
Peter.
You've got to get out of here.
Don't be looking for me. No, no, no, no.
Please just stay with me. Come on. Hold
on. Come on. Please.
Peter.
Peter. Peter.
Look at me.
Shock today.
A Spider-Man arrived at Bellevue
Hospital with a bullet wound.
Seemingly a death story.
The reclusive crime fighter is in
critical condition as the city's top
medical experts work to save him.
Tonight, all eyes are on Spider-Man.
The hero who saved New York so many
times is now in the hands of its best
and brightest.
And the people of New York hold their
breath.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Hey. Where's my
dad?
Where's my dad?
I got you covered.
You're good.
Where's Jean? Is she okay?
Yeah, she's okay.
She's okay. Where is she?
I think maybe she just left.
She was, uh, using her magic voodoo shit
to keep you alive.
Yeah.
She's alright.
I'm really sorry for what I did. I know
it's a lot of things, but here's the
thing, okay?
I think... I think
your bravery killed my day.
But that... That was something else.
Are you crying?
No.
I ain't good.
You know, you look the exact way I
thought you would.
You're a nice kid.
I've never had a friend like that.
And we're friends now.
I can't believe I just saw you cry.
What am I talking about?
Bullshit.
Oh, Jeff.
I've been doing it all night.
Been here since you walked in. Take a
look.
No kidding.
We came in there to cut through the
suit, but...
When you're ready to split, I got a
plan.
I'm thinking a lot about what you said.
And you'd be happy to know that I've
decided I'm not... I'm not gonna do this
alone anymore.
A little pain in my back, but I could
probably get back out there if you need
me for anything.
What I need you to do is rest.
I know, I know, but come on, you gotta
give me something. I mean, how's the
investigation going?
Well, the minister's still missing.
Your friend, Black Boydall, she's been
helping us get through all the records.
Damage control, trying to have scrubs.
Had me dropped by her office the other
day, and I was back.
Well, my skin feels amazing.
Attention all units, we have a confirmed
bank robbery in progress.
Hey, are you getting this?
Yeah, I'm on it. Hey, it's not that far
from here. I could probably meet you
down there.
No, we can handle a robbery.
Just try to take care of yourself.
Okay.
You do it.
Say hello to E.J. Marley for me.
Okay.
Spider-Man says hello.
Hey. Oh, whoa.
Flower guy, right? From the party?
I'm Peter.
Okay, hello.